zengaming.co 2016-10-30

# zengaming

### Privacy Policy

Last Updated: December, 2015

Please read this privacy policy carefully. By signing up with our website or otherwise accessing, or using it, you acknowledge that you have read, understand, agree and accept all the terms of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please cease use of this website. 

Zengaming Inc. and its affiliates ("Zengaming") respect your privacy and take your rights seriously. We provide you with this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information We receives from users ("User") to our Site and Services (“Site”). 

Zengaming reserves the right to make any changes to this Policy at any time, notice of which may be posted on this privacy page at www.zengaming.co/privacy. We encourage periodic review of our Privacy Policy for any changes in order to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the information we collect. The last amendments will be reflected in the "Last Updated" heading. The continued use of the Site following the posting of any amendments will be deemed as acceptance of those amendments. 

1\. **Information Collection.** While using this Site, Users may provide Zengaming with personally identifiable information. This refers to information about Users that can be used to contact or identify a User, and information on a User's use of and activities on the Site ("Personal Information"). Personal Information that Zengaming collects may include, but is not limited to, a User's name, email address, nationality, photo, payment information and your credentials with a designated third party website or services, messages you sent to other users (including photos, location, audio or video files) or any other information you voluntarily submit to us. When a User visits the Site, our servers automatically record information that the browser sends whenever a User visits a website. This information may include, but is not limited to, a User's computer’s Internet Protocol address (IP address), browser type, operating system your device uses, geo-location information, and the web page the User was visiting before arriving on the Site. Zengaming uses “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to a User's computer’s hard disk to facilitate your computer’s future access to this information. “Persistent cookies” are utilized to save a User's user ID and login password to facilitate future logins. Zengaming uses cookies to better understand how our Users interact with the Site, to monitor usage and how traffic arrives at the Site, and to improve the functionality of the Site. 

2\. **How We Use Personal Information.** Personal Information is used: \- to provide and improve the Site, services, features and content;  
\- to administer a User's membership and use of the Site;  
\- to enable Users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site;  
\- to better understand User needs and interests;  
\- to fulfill requests a User may make;  
\- to personalize the User experience;  
\- to respond to Users' requests and feedbacks;  
\- to provide or offer updates and product announcements;  
\- to provide Users with further information and offers from Zengaming that Zengaming believes Users may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information on services and products offered by Zengaming or third parties that are authorized by Zengaming; and  
\- to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. 

Personal Information is gathered to monitor and analyze use of Zengaming and its services, for technical administration, to increase the Site’s functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to User needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of Users, and to verify that the proper information is submitted to fulfill and process User requests. If a User decides at any time that they no longer wish to receive Zengaming emails or communications, they should click on the unsubscribe link provided in Zengaming's marketing emails or email support@Zengaming.co with subject line "unsubscribe." 

3\. **How We Share Personal Information.** We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Zengaming Site and service, to provide service on Zengaming's behalf, to perform website-related services (including but not limited to maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of Zengaming’s features), or to assist Zengaming in analyzing how the Site and service are used and can be improved. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf. 

Zengaming may transmit or store Personal Information, in different locations around the world, in particular outside the European Union and California, USA. In such circumstances, we will strive to ensure that adequate measures are put in place in order to protect the User's confidentiality and rights with respect to Personal Information. You hereby provide us with your express consent to such transfer or storage of your Personal Information. If you are a resident of California, United States, or of the European Union, you have the right to send us written request and ask for a list of Personal Information categories that we may disclosed to third parties or to which we may provided your assent for third parties' access, and the details of such third parties. To exercise such right you may contact us at: support@Zengaming.co. 

4\. **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement.** Zengaming must cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. In the event of a claim and/or legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Zengaming or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity Zengaming may consider to pose a risk of being illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable, Zengaming reserves the right to disclose any Personal Information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as Zengaming in its sole discretion finds necessary or appropriate. 

5\. **Business Transfers.** In the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, Zengaming may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, and our Users' Personal Information may be transferred as part of that transaction. 

6\. **Changing or Deleting Your Information.** You may review or update certain fields of your User account at any time by accessing the settings page. You may also change your email address or password associated with your account or delete your User account entirely from Zengaming.co. Users may opt to unsubscribe from our email alerts, which will terminate the issuance of automatically generated emails that inform Users about new features of the Site or to market Zengaming's services. 

You may remove our cookies by following the instructions of your operating platform or your browser preferences. You may also refrain from providing us with any information you do not feel comfortable sharing. However, please be advised that failure of providing us with certain information may result in our inability to provide you the full features of our Service. 

7\. **Children Information.** We will not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13, we will remove its information from our servers. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that children are not using the Service. 

8\. **Security.** Zengaming takes the security of Personal Information seriously. Zengaming appreciates our Users' use of the Site and will employ reasonable measures designed to protect Personal Information from unauthorized access and unsolicited contact from third-party groups. Credit card numbers are not stored or held on our servers. 

While we strive to use commercially acceptable means and procedures to protect the information, which considerably reduce the risks of data misuse, we cannot guarantee that our systems will be absolutely safe. If you become aware of any security vulnerability or potential data breach, please contact us immediately, and we will take the appropriate measures to address such incident, as deemed necessary. 

9\. **Third Party Websites.** Users may find advertising or other content on our Service that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Service. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Service, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Zengaming at team@Zengaming.com.
